你觉得达伦・贾维斯怎么样
What do you think of Darren Jarvis?
CBS: 哥伦比亚广播公司
-CBS的吗  -他想聘我作记者
- At CBS? - He wants me to be a correspondent.
不值得
Not worth your time.
MSNBC: 微软全国有线广播电视公司
MSNBC的格里尔・菲舍呢
What about Greer Fisher at MSNBC?
继续撰稿
Stick to writing.
电视只作为副业
Do TV on the side.
你作主播大材小用了
You're more than a talking head.
-去头条网呢  -那是什么地方
- How about Slugline? - What's Slugline?
如果政治新闻网要雇我  你觉得怎么样
If I said Politico wanted to hire me, what would you say?
我觉得那还有点意思
I would say that that peaks my interest.
半年后的头条网
Six months from now,
就是一年半前的政治新闻网
Slugline will be what Politico was a year and a half ago.
政治新闻网的人都看头条网
Everyone at Politico reads it,
因为头条网的报道总比他们快
because Slugline's breaking stories before they are.
我怎么从没听说过
I wonder why I've never heard of it.
头条网的记者都是自由撰稿人
Everyone's a free agent.
报道什么都行  随时随地撰稿
They write whatever they want, wherever they are.
很多人直接用手机写稿
Most people write from their phones.
如果他们给你自由和曝光率
Well, if freedom and exposure are what they're offering,
我觉得值得一试
I would say that is a meeting worth taking.
汉默施密特的事开始爆发了
This Hammerschmidt thing is blowing up.
我觉得他可能会被解雇
I think he might get fired.
推特上起码有上千条评论
There's gotta be 1,000 tweets here.
支持我的  诋毁我的
People defending me, people trashing me.
甚至还有个标签  "佐伊加油"
There's even a hashtag-- "Gozoe."
可不能留下蛛丝马迹
We mustn't leave any trails.
可我的联络人都在里面啊
All of my contacts are in there.
那你就该去找些新联络人了
Then it's time for you to get some new contacts.
别担心  我会给你买部新的  买两部新的
Don't worry. I'll get you a phone. I'll get you two, in fact.
一部工作  一部一次性的用于娱乐
One for work and a burner for play.
等着下午签收吧
Expect them this afternoon.
对了  佐伊  加油
Oh, and go, Zoe.
是那个记者吗
The reporter?
是的
Yes.
就这一次吗
Just this once?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
她能为我们做什么
What does she offer us?
能在必要时替我们传话
A mouthpiece when we need one.
到目前为止她很有帮助
She's been very useful so far.
-她想换取什么  -门路
- What does she want? - Access.
地位
A seat at the table.
听起来是她的收益比较大
Sounds like she's getting the better side of the bargain.
我能控制她
She can be controlled.
你确定
Are you sure?
是的  我保证
She can. I promise you.
好吧  但愿如此
Okay. If you say so.
如果你让我结束...
The moment you want me to end it--
我知道  弗兰西斯
I know, Francis.
我该准备一下去上班了
I should get ready for work.
我以为你过会儿才会来
Didn't think you'd be in till later.
这是你今天的日程表
This is your agenda for the day.
这是这周的日程表
Here's your schedule for the rest of the week.
这些是需要你批准和签署的文件
These are papers that need to be approved or signed.
这里是委员会会议的提纲
Over here are your one-sheets for committee meetings
和随后立法工作的简报
and briefs on upcoming legislative action.
我跟艾什利交待了  在你找到替任者前她会替我
I filled Ashley in. She can cover until you find a replacement.
克里斯蒂娜
Christina...
怎么了
What?
谢谢你
Thank you...
把这些都整理好了
for getting all this in order.
如果对桌上的文件
Ashley can call me
有什么问题  可以让艾什利打电话问我
if you have any questions about what's on your desk.
他已经到了吗
Is he here yet?
我请他在办公室等你了
I put him in your office.
马蒂・斯比奈拉是教师工会的首席说客
Marty Spinella, head lobbyist for the teachers' union.
他恨不得拧断我的头  剥我的皮
He wants to rip my head off and peel it like an orange.
为什么  因为我对他撒谎了  可我也没办法
Why? Because I lied to him. But what choice did I have
如果我说真话  那就没得可谈判了
when the truth would've ended the conversation before it began?
-我等会儿打给你  -马蒂
- I'll call you back. - Marty.
你竟然骗我  弗兰克
You fucking lied, Frank?
不  你是当面骗我
No, no. You lied to my fucking face?
-马蒂  我没撒谎  -没有是吧
- Marty, I did not lie. - Did not--
我们整个周末都待在那间会议室里
We spent the whole weekend in that room
一条一条地讨论这项法案
pouring over this bill line by line,
但里面完全没提到集体谈判
and nowhere did it say anything about collective bargaining.
镇定点  坐下来  我们好好谈谈
Let's calm down and sit down, and we will discuss this.
我会对一切作出解释
I will explain everything that's going on,
不管花多长时间  我们会把这事谈妥的
and we will talk it out no matter how long it takes.
不  不用长谈了
No, no more. This is gonna be a very short meeting,
因为摆在你面前的只有两条路
'cause only one of two things are gonna happen:
要么你立即向我保证删除那条修正案
either you assure me right now that amendment is out,
要么我这就离开
or I'm walking out that door
然后开始回击你
and I'm gonna start launching missiles.
我们本来也没想把修正案留在法案里
The amendment was never intended to stay in the bill.
它只是个筹码  仅此而已
It was just there for leverage, that's all.
你威胁要减少联邦政府对
You threatened to cut federal funding
公立学校的拨款啊
from union school districts?
那可不是筹码  弗兰克
That's not a poker chip, Frank.
那就是颗脏弹
That's a goddamn dirty bomb.
修正案不会留在法案里
Look, the amendment is not staying in the bill.
我只求在绩效标准上有个商量
I just need you to work with me on performance standards.
绩效标准
Performance standards?
你什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
你已经答应删掉这条
You agreed that they were already out!
怎么能出尔反尔
You can't just put them back in!
-马蒂  听我说  -我还要维护我的声誉
- Marty, look-- - I have a reputation to uphold!
你在加夫尼玩你的大桃子时
I am the one that made the union reps stay here for you
是我帮你把工会代表留在了这儿
while you were in Gaffney playing with your fucking Peachoid!
-马蒂  -马上告诉我  到底留不留那条
- Marty-- - You tell me right now! Is that amendment in or out?
我们可以相互妥协  马蒂
There is a middle ground here, Marty.
我们只需找到平衡点
We just have to find it.
那就还是要了
I take that as a no.
好吧
Okay.
马蒂  别挑起一场你必输的仗
Marty, do not start a war you know you're gonna lose.
你耍我  我就奉陪到底
You fuck me, I fuck back.
斯坦普
Stamper!
马蒂与我一直合作愉快
Marty and I have a good working relationship.
至少曾经愉快  他脾气不小
Or used to. You can see he has a temper,
但我通常都能做通他工作
but I can usually cut through that and reason with him.
我可能逼人太甚了  有点令人担心
But I may have pushed him too far, which is worrisome.
反目的朋友是最可怕的敌人
Friends make the worst enemies.
-怎么样  -你听到了什么
- How'd it go? - What did you hear?
-叫骂  -那不就是了
- A lot of "fucks." - Well, that pretty much says it.
我们好好想想
Let's think this through.
我们得参加民主党全国委员会首脑会晤
We've got the D.N.C. leadership meeting.
-什么  -本来你不非得去
- What? - I'd say you could skip it,
但博奇刚把这任务丢给我们
but Birch just dumped it on us.
-什么时候  -在这里  12分钟后
- When? - It's here in 12 minutes.
为什么要在这里不在总部
Why here and not the D.N.C. headquarters?
总部正在装修
The D.N.C. is doing renovations.
他们要改造得节能环保
They're gonna be green energy efficient.
真会花党内资金
Oh, that's a charming use of party funds.
我们刚搬来三个月
We've only been in this space about three months.
真棒
It's cool.
和《先驱报》差很多吧
Not exactly the Herald, is it?
你去过他们办公室吗
Have you been to those offices?
去过  真让人想切腕
Yes. Wrist-slitting was in order.
还有谁找过你
So, who else is courting you?
-有那么几个  -那就是都有了
- A few people. - You mean everyone.
早上的确收到不少邮件
There were a lot of e-mails this morning.
不难想象  现在你风头正旺
That's not surprising. You're having a moment.
很多人对你感兴趣  我也是其中之一
People are interested. I'm one of them.
一件事做8分钟  我就会觉得无聊
But if eight minutes passes on anything, I get bored.
8分钟后  我可能会觉得你无聊
In eight minutes, I can be bored with you,
除非你能不断激起我的兴趣
unless you keep me interested.
我觉得你能做到
I think you can.
而这个地方
And I think this is the place
能让你抓住整个世界的兴趣
for you to keep the rest of the world interested too.
决定权在你  我不会死皮赖脸
It's your call. I won't chase you.
这很吸引我
I'm definitely tempted.
你随便逛
Take as long as you want to look around.
薪酬数发给我  我会回电告诉你还价
E-mail me your figure. I'll call you back with a counter.
这几个是重点
This is our top priority--
此三州都是大选中的摇摆州
俄亥俄  佛罗里和宾夕法尼亚
Ohio, Florida, and Pennsylvania.
必须全部搞定  否则沃克无法连任
We need all of them, or Walker's a one-term president.
他选马修斯为竞选伙伴就是为了宾州
Pennsylvania is why he picked Matthews as a running mate.
但我们现在得找个替任
But now we have to find a replacement.
补选在11月
The special election is this November.
帕特里夏・惠特克  民主党全国委员会主席
Patricia Whittaker, D.N.C. Chair.
极少数用大脑而不是屁股
A rare example of someone whose head is in the game
思考的人
instead of up their backside.
能力在这群人中凤毛麟角
Competence is such an exotic bird in these woods
每碰到有能力的人我都很欣赏
that I appreciate it whenever I see it.
对国会也有影响
This also affects the House.
新州长将负责重划选区
The new governor will oversee redistricting.
在这儿丢了席位
We lose seats here,
会导致在国会失去多数席位
that means we could lose our majority in Washington.
共和党支持杰克・斯沃夫  匹兹堡的前市长
Well,the R.N.C. is backing Jack Swofford,ex-Mayor of Pittsburgh.
他在全州有知名度
He's got statewide name recognition
竞选也准备充分
and campaign machinery in place.
三个月过去了  我们却还没有人选
It's been three months, and we don't have dick.
那个司法部长怎么样  本・普拉克特
What about the A.G.? Ben Pluckett?
不行  本14年要竞选参议员
No. Ben's got his eyes set on the senate in '14.
他不会成功的
Which he'll lose because
他去年搞砸了一起性侵钓鱼执法的案子
he botched a sex offender sting last year.
-麦克霍兰德总可以吧  -他78了
- There's always McHolland. - He's 78.
上次他在职的时候  卡特还是总统吧
When's the last time he held office, when Carter was president?
里根  不过差不多
Reagan, but same difference.
他受人尊敬  举止庄重
He has dignity, he has gravitas.
如果要找人替马修斯的话
If you need someone to fill Matthews' shoes--
我们根本就不该找人去代替马修斯
You can't fill Jim Matthews' shoes, so we shouldn't even try.
得找张新面孔
We need a fresh face.
但这个州的候选人都不怎么样
The state has a weak bench.
那就一个个过现任议员
Let's go through all the sitting Congressmen one by one
看看有没有谁脱颖而出
and see if anybody sticks out from the crowd.
名单在这里
All right. I got the list right here.
很好  开始
Okay. Go ahead.
宾夕法尼亚第一选区  彼得・罗素
Pennsylvania's first district, Peter Russo.
划掉  他不行  没经验  能力一般
Cross him off. He's no good. No experience, no chops.
继续  第二选区  格温多林・皮尔斯
Okay, moving on. Second district, Gwendolyn Pierce.
格温争议太大  在堕胎问题上太极端
Nah, Gwen's too controversial. Very vocal on abortion.
-卡洛琳呢  -她不错
- And Caroline? - She's good.
-小伙子们怎么样  -你问他们四个
- And the boys? - All fucking four of 'em?
你养四张嘴试试
You feed 'em.
你手机上有他们的照片吗
You got any pictures on your phone?
得了  彼得  就别废话了  好吗
Come on. Let's cut the shit, Pete, will ya?
船厂你打算怎么办
What are we gonna do about the shipyard?
军事基地整合委员会的听证会已经结束了
BRAC had their hearing.
他们要关闭那里
They slated it for closing.
你当时怎么不作证
Yeah, and why didn't you testify?
这可是12000个工作岗位
We're talking 12,000 jobs here.
我也没办法  保罗  有人要关掉它
My hands were tied, Paul. People wanted it closed.
-我压力很大  -谁给你的压力
- I was under a lot of pressure. - From who?
位高权重的人
People high up the food chain.
-我无能为力  -放屁
- There was nothing I could do. - That's bullshit!
你去找委员会  和外交部交涉
You go back to BRAC. You talk to the D.O.D.
找海军部长谈  总之做点什么
You talk to the Secretary of the Navy. You do something.
不可能
It's not gonna happen.
-为什么  -我说了  政治原因
- Okay. Why not? - I told you. It's political.
好  那你让我回造船厂协会
Okay, So I'm supposed to go back to the shipbuilders' association
怎么跟他们说
and say what now exactly?
他们都因为彼得・罗素的弄权而丢了工作吗
That they're out of work because Pete Russo's playing politics?
天呐  彼得
I mean, Jesus, Pete.
是我们支持你赢得了选举
We're the ones who got you fucking elected in the first place.
现在你却要背叛我们
Now you're gonna turn your back on us?
你该走了
You should go.
你说真的
Seriously?
我才刚到  你就赶我走
I just got here. You're kicking me out now?
我在和你说话
Hey, I'm fucking talking to you!
我以为我们是一起长大的朋友
I thought we grew up together.
但这个坐在大办公桌后面的人
But this guy sitting behind his big desk...
我根本不知道他是谁
I don't even know who the fuck he is.
那个被逼入绝境
Where's the Pete Russo who knew how
也要誓死反抗的彼得哪去了
to throw a punch when his back was against the wall?
那个人才是我的朋友
That guy was my friend.
放假前一个月拉拢整个国家的老师
Every teacher in the country a month before school ends?
不用全拉拢  15  20个州就足够了
Doesn't need all of them. 15, 20 states, that's all.
美国教师联合会和全国教育协会向来有分歧
The A.F.T. And the N.E.A. can't agree on anything.
你低估了马蒂・斯比奈拉的能力
You underestimate Marty Spinella.
那我们去找谁
So which one do we target?
全国教育协会的可能性更高
We have a better chance with the N.E.A.
你认为查克・斯隆会上钩
You think Chuck Sloan will bite?
合作  我们就保护你的人
Cooperate-- we'll give your people protection
提升你的地位
and a place at the banquet.
反抗  我们就毁了你
Fight us, we break you.
他会上钩的  给他打电话
He'll bite. Get him on the phone.
现在凌晨两点多了
It's after 2:00.
斯比奈拉正在策动
Spinella is potentially mobilizing
美国历史上最大规模的教师罢工
the largest teachers' strike in United States history.
-没人睡得着  -我这就打给他
- Nobody's sleeping. - I'll call him right now.
抱歉  我们声音太大了吗
I'm sorry. Are we being too loud?
有点
A little.
-你在忙什么  -庆典
- What are you working on? - The gala.
要做的事太多
There's so much to do.
-南茜把我的名单发给你了吗  -发了
- Did Nancy send you my list? - She did.
-你怎么看  -名单不错
- What'd you think? - It's a good list.
谢谢你邀请他们
Thanks for inviting them.
有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
还是没法和雷米提出的价码比
It's still not anywhere near what Remy brought to the table.
桑科提的数是150万美元  弗兰西斯
Sancorp offered 1.5 million, Francis.
我在计算  只能弄到50万左右
I'm adding up the numbers, and we're only at half a million.
-我接通查克的电话了  -稍等
- I got Chuck on the phone. - In a minute.
我可以再打几个电话
I can make more calls.
能筹到150万吗
Enough to raise a million-five?
至少可以接近这个数字
I can at least get us closer.
我去睡觉了
I'm going to bed.
别动这些东西
Don't move any of this around.
克莱尔  我们一致决定了拒绝雷米
Claire, we made the decision to turn Remy down.
我没强迫你
No one forced you.
我以为这事已经过去了
I thought we were okay on this.
你说的没错
You're right.
晚安  弗兰西斯
Good night, Francis.
我是亚当  请留言
This is Adam. Leave a message.
你好  亚当  是我  我知道很晚了
Hi, Adam. It's me. I know it's late,
我只是想打电话
but, well, I was really just calling
再次感谢你的照片
to thank you again for the photographs.
它们一定会在拍卖会上大卖
I'm sure they're gonna be a big hit at the auction.
祝你安好
I hope you're well.
它们一定会在拍卖会上大卖
I'm sure they're gonna be a big hit at the auction.
祝你安好
I hope you're well.
这边走  汉默施密特先生
Right this way, Mr. Hammerschmidt.
他来了
He's here.
下午好  汤姆
Good afternoon, Tom.
律师
Legal?
你说了  还是没说
Did you say it, or didn't you?
对你以及所有问这个问题的人
To you and to anyone who asks,
是的  我说了
yes, I did.
我们真的需要他们吗
Do we really need them?
除非你要找我的麻烦
Not unless I should expect a fight.
我不会
You shouldn't.
请让我们单独待会儿
Give us a few moments.
重点不在于你怎么骂她了
It's not what you called her,
而是在于你辞退了她
it's that you let her leave the building.
我知道怎么运作报社  玛格丽特
I know how to run a paper, Margaret.
但我不知道怎么跟
What I don't know how to do
不听话的员工一起运作报社
is run a paper staffed with people I can't control.
真有那么严重吗
Was she really out of control?
据我了解  她不过是拒绝了一个新职位
To my understanding, she simply turned down a new position.
是态度  她拒绝时的态度
It's her attitude. It's the way she turned it down.
你问过她更想做什么吗
Did you think to ask her what she'd rather do instead?
-难道要我迎合我的雇员  -是我的雇员
- Is it my job to pander to all my employees-- - My employees.
如果他们能提供你给不了东西
And if they have something to offer that you don't,
没错  你就得迎合
yes, it is your job.
我们谈过的  汤姆
We've been through this, Tom.
报社在亏损
The paper's operating at a loss.
我们需要佐伊这样的人
We need people like Zoe.
我很清楚我们的处境  玛格丽特
I'm very aware of how much we're hurting, Margaret.
裁员  削减发行量
Staff reductions, dip in circulation.
一想到他们的脸
Each one of those faces
和每个失去的订户
and every subscriber we lose,
我晚上就睡不着觉
they keep me awake at night.
生意上的事我不插嘴
Now, I won't argue the business side of things.
我既没资格  也不擅长
It's neither my place nor my area of expertise,
但要知道
but know this--
佐伊・巴恩斯  推特  博客
Zoe Barnes, Twitter, blogs,
泛滥的媒体
enriched media,
这些都太肤浅了
they're all surface.
不过是昙花一现
They're fads.
这些既不是这份报纸的根基
They aren't the foundation this paper was built on,
也不会让它繁荣
and they aren't what will keep it alive.
我们的核心读者渴望严肃新闻
We have a core readership that thirsts for hard news.
为了他们我才每周工作80小时
Those are the people I work 80 hours a week for.
我不会被时尚左右
And I won't be distracted by what's fashionable.
那是你的辞职信
That's your resignation letter.
出去时拿给律师
Hand it to the lawyers on the way out.
我让你自己待会儿吧
I'll give you some privacy.
不用了  你留下吧  我马上就好
No, no, stay. It'll be quick.
我们俩喝一杯
We'll get a drink.
我们先在华盛顿展开罢工
We're going to launch right here in Washington.
当放羊的学生都涌上街头
We'll see how Congress likes it when the streets are
看国会是个什么反应
teaming with unsupervised school kids.
然后逐渐在全国铺开
Then we'll phase out the rest of the country.
大家等我一分钟
Everybody hold on for one minute.
什么事
What's up?
全国教育协会不干了
The N.E.A. is out.
等等  什么
Hang on.What?
他们撤出了
They pulled out.
为什么
Why?
他不肯说
He wouldn't say.
再等一分钟
Hold on for one more minute.
立刻接通查克・斯隆的电话
Chuck Sloan-- get him on the phone right now.
他已经在线了
I've got him right here.
-静音了吗  -是的
- Is he muted? - Yes.
你好  查克  我是马蒂
Hey, Chuck. It's Marty.
听着  你不能这么做
Listen, you can't do this.
要是我们现在不团结  就没有
If we don't stay united now, we don't have a--
你雇我来维护你的利益  对吗
You hired me to represent your interests, right?
你这样我还怎么为教师游说
How can I possibly lobby for the teachers
让国会看到我们连个联合罢工都做不到
when Congress sees us splintering before we even put up a unite--
好吧
All right.
安德伍德找过你了
Did Underwood get to you?
弗兰克满口谎话  手段狡猾
Whoa, Frank is dishonest and manipulative.
你知道他已经骗过我们一次了
You've seen that he's lied to us already.
等等  查克  查克
Wait-whoa-whoa-whoa, Chuck, Ch-Ch-Chuck?
查克
Chuck!
狗娘养的混蛋
Son of a bitch!
-你在哪里  -办公室
- Where are you? - I'm at the office.
-不对  -你不信我
- False. - You don't believe me?
-不信  -你在哪
- Not for a second. - Where are you?
-正要去见人  -见谁
- About to walk into a meeting. - With who?
某个我要惩罚的人
Someone I have to punish.
-告诉我名字  -不说
- Give me a name. - No name.
这人做错了什么
What did this person do wrong?
骗我
Lie to me.
你要怎样惩罚他
How will you punish him?
你为什么觉得是个男的
What makes you think it's a him?
等等  我接个电话
Hold on. I have to take this.
你在哪
Where are you?
我  反正不在办公室
Me? I am not at the office.
你要每周都给我个新手机吗
You're going to give me a new one of these every week?
我不能继续...
Well, I-- I can't continue to--
得有保护措施才行
Not without protection.
没人能管我该做什么
Nobody tells me when to work and when to play.
我不是不讲理  佐伊
I'm not being unreasonable, Zoe.
你要是不信我  我们就不该这么做
If you can't trust me, we shouldn't be doing this at all.
好吧  那我们要怎么建立信任呢
Well, then, how do we establish our trust?
我一直很谨慎
I have been very discreet.
职业习惯  好啊
Oh, professional discretion, yes,
但这你没经验
but this is new territory.
你的手机有摄像头
You have a camera on your phone.
拍照吧
Pictures...
那种不能让爸爸看到的照片
The kind I wouldn't want my father to see.
尺度得再大点
Well, I'm going to need more than that.
躺下
Lie back.
有点想象力
Use your imagination.
把行李都收拾好准备明天走
I want everything packed for tomorrow.
-我们检查过了  爸爸  -真的吗
- We checked already, dad. - Oh, did you?
厨房台面上的粉红耐克是我的吗
Those are my pink Nikes on the kitchen counter?
还有你  汽车人
And you, Autobot,
擎天柱怎么在我床底下呢
what is Optimus Prime doing under my bed?
你明天出发前
He better transform himself
他最好变形进你的行李里
into your backpack before you have to leave tomorrow.
爸爸
Hey, dad?
克里斯蒂娜还会回来吗
Is Christina coming back?
我想不会了  宝贝  不会了
Um, I don't think so, buddy. No.
我喜欢她
Oh, I liked her.
我也是  她挺不错
Me, too. She's cool.
是啊
Yeah, she is cool.
你们得刷牙了
And you guys gotta brush your teeth
然后再把房间检查一遍
and then check the rooms again,
就可以上床睡觉了
and then it's time for bed.
懂了吗  小南瓜们
Got it, pumpkins?
爸爸  我讨厌你叫我们小南瓜
Dad, you know I hate it when you call us pumpkins.
快去  否则把你们做成南瓜派
Go before I turn you into a pie.
彼得・罗素
Peter Russo.
他是个酒鬼
He's a drunk.
他目前是  而且很能干
He is at the moment, a very functional one.
想想他戒酒会是什么样子
Imagine if he was sober.
即使如此  你让他去竞选州长
Even so, you run him for governor,
人们会去翻他的前科
people are going to dig into his past.
那我们就化劣势为优势
Well, we turn that into an asset, not a liability.
曾经堕落  现在脱胎换骨了
Here's who I was. Here's who I am now.
你也看到首脑会晤上
You saw how they dismissed him
他们想都没想就否定了他
in three seconds at the leadership meeting.
帕特・惠特克非常开明
Patty Whittaker is very open-minded,
而我又很善于说服别人
and I am very persuasive.
罗素有这意思吗
You think Russo even wants it?
能从费城南部的街道
Any kid who's made it from the streets of South Philly
爬到国会圆形大厅的人都有野心
to the Capitol Rotunda is ambitious.
我们只要激起这份野心
We just need to tap into that,
给他最优秀的人才
surround him with the best people
建立好团队  就能一发冲天
and then build the machine and push the go button.
那你觉得他能赢
So you think he could win.
我认为他有能力一争
I think he can be a contender.
好吧  假设奇迹出现了  他赢了
Okay, let's say we pull off a miracle and he wins.
这对我们有什么好处
What do we gain by it?
掌控着这场竞选
Isn't it better to be holding the reins in this race
不比当个旁观者好吗
than watching from the stands?
你夫人来电
You wife is on the phone.
接进来
Put her through in here.
我明白宾州对选区重划的重要性
I understand that Pennsylvania's important for redistricting--
不  不仅是为了竞选  道格
No, no, no, this isn't just about this race, Doug.
开拓思路
Expand your thinking.
还有谁是宾州人
Who else is from Pennsylvania?
不对  不是众议院里的人
No, no, no, not in Congress.
而是行政部门
The executive branch.
副总统
The vice president.
亲爱的你好
Hello, my dear.
南希拿我的西装去干洗了
Nancy had my tux dry-cleaned
这样我就不会...
so I won't embarrass--
科茨沃斯酒店取消了我的预约
The Cotesworth cancelled on us.
我马上就出发去接你
I'm leaving right now. I'll come get you.
我得走了
I've got to go.
出什么事了
What's going on?
今晚庆典的酒店
The hotel, for tonight's gala.
他们不让克莱尔的人进宴会厅
They refused to let Claire into the ballroom
因为他们的雇员是工会的
because their employees are union.
斯比奈拉
Spinella.
他怎么冲我来都可以
Yeah, he can go after me all he wants,
居然动我老婆
but to go after my wife?
真下作  我们在科茨沃斯酒店碰面
No class. Meet me at the Cotesworth.
好的
You got it.
为什么不干脆去别处办
Why can't we just move it to another place?
我查过了  到处都有预约了
I looked into that. Everything's booked.
这种事得提前几周预约
You have to reserve these things weeks in advance.
我让斯坦普在网上找其他地点
I've got Stamper online looking for another venue somewhere.
弗兰西斯  货运卡车已经到科茨沃斯酒店了
Francis, the delivery trucks are already at the Cotesworth.
我总不能让大家改去别的地方
I can't have people showing up at a different place
万一有人没收到通知邮件怎么办
in case they don't get the email.
都是我的错  我很内疚
This is my fault. I feel awful.
这可事关50万
There's a half a million on the line here.
这我知道
I realize that.
我不能总让我的工作
And I can't keep having my work
因为你的而受影响
take these hits on behalf of yours.
这已经不是小麻烦了
It's more than just an inconvenience.
我知道  问题会解决的
I know. We'll solve it.
-我收到了你的邮件  -觉得怎样
- Hey, I just got your email. - What did you think?
发稿不需要先经过我
You don't have to send me things before you post.
我以为你会想先看一下
Oh, I thought you might want to take a look.
我们的目标是让我来不及读
The goal here is for everyone to post things
你们就发布了
faster than I have a chance to read them.
只要你自己满意  就可以发布
If you're satisfied with the article, just put it up.
-好的  -你满意吗
- Okay. - Are you satisfied?
我觉得还行
I think so.
好吧  要么满意要么不满意
Okay, you are or you aren't.
《先驱报》逼你耍的那些把式
Whatever hoops the Herald made you jump through--
-我知道  -忘掉就好
- I know. - ...Let them go.
固执己见没什么错  佐伊
It's okay to be opinionated, Zoe,
出去挖新闻也没什么错
and it's okay to go outside to get your hands dirty.
你不需要坐在桌前
You're no longer tied to a desk.
或者是那个垫子
Or that pillow, for that matter.
我不发了
I'm not going to post it.
中期预测不算新闻
Midterm predictions-- they're not news.
纯属胡扯
They're bullshit.
我同意
Well, I agree.
我可以做得更好
I can do better.
我相信你可以
I think you can.
欢迎你给我惊喜
Feel free to blow my mind.
如果我们接这个活儿  全体员工就罢工
If we do this event, the whole staff walks out.
我有三百位客人
I've got 300 guests--
你和我太太签了合同
You signed a contract with my wife.
我们会把钱退给您太太的组织
We'll refund your wife's organization
并补偿将活动移至更合适地点的
and pay for whatever the costs of moving the event to a more
一切费用
appropriate venue.
我们得退回50万美元的捐款
And we would have to refund a half a million dollars in donations.
这个你们也能补偿吗
Can you pay for that, too?
因为我确信这是致损原因
Because I'm pretty sure there's cause for damages here.
十分抱歉  先生
I truly apologize, sir.
你老板是谁
Who's your boss?
我请示过业主们
I spoke with the owners,
他们允许我来做最佳选择
and they authorized me to do what I think is best.
那他们知道他们将41名国会议员
And do they realize that they are shutting the door on 41 members
拒之门外了吗
of the United States Congress?
是的  先生  他们明白
Yes, sir, they do.
我做了一个非常艰难的判断
I had to make a very hard judgment call.
我严重质疑你的判断能力
Well, I seriously question your judgment.
要知道  话传得很快
You know, word travels fast in this town.
那么多午餐会  会议和晚宴
All those luncheons and conventions and dinners.
失去这么多生意真是可惜
It's going to be a shame to lose all that work. Isn't it?
议员  您说的很对
Congressman, you are absolutely right,
但是如果我的员工罢工  我
but if my staff walks out, I--
请您理解我的窘境
Please understand the predicament I'm in.
我有办法了
I got an idea.
我知道该怎么办了
I know what we're going to do.
亲爱的  他们不让我们进去办
Honey, they're not going to let us have it inside.
我们就在这儿办
We're going to have it right here
在他们门前阶上  办成野餐会
on their front steps, picnic style.
需要我做什么
What do you need from me?
人力
I need your manpower.
是  先生  马上照办
Yes, sir, I'm on it.
注意  放下手头的工作  听好了
Okay, everybody, stop what you're doing, and listen up.
喂
Yeah.
你好  弗兰克
Oh, hey, Frank.
-多久  -三小时左右
- How soon? - About three hours.
-多少人  -只有三百个
- How many people we talking? - Just 300.
花店会把所有的存货都送来
The florist is going to send over whatever he has.
很好
Great.
弗兰西斯  食品怎样了
Francis, where are we with food?
我订到了热狗  比萨饼  还有南方黑人食品
I've got hotdogs, pizzas, and soul food coming,
可能还有别的
maybe something else.
姑娘们  我是这么想的
Girls, here's what I want.
四个吧台  每层两个
I want four bars, two on each level.
食品放在那边  无声拍卖在这边
The food can go there. The silent auction goes here.
取消弦乐四重奏  找个DJ
Oh, and cancel the string quartet. Let's get a DJ.
道格  酒怎么样了
Doug, how are we on booze?
-酒桶已经送过来了  -很好
- Kegs are on the way now. - Great.
打电话去办公室找丹妮丝
Oh, and call Denise at the office
让她把所有的捐款信封都带来
and have her bring every donation envelope she can find.
留言都给我
Okay, messages, people.
罗素议员办公室
Congressman Russo's office.
是的  麻烦等一下  谢谢
Yes, can you hold one minute? Thank you.
议员先生  大家都打电话问造船厂的事
Congressman, people keep calling about the shipyards.
我们不知道该怎么说
We don't know what to tell them.
就只说会转达留言
We just say we'll give you the message.
-继续这么说  -都在这儿
- Keep saying that. - Here they are,
留言还有所有邮件
the messages and all the emails we've gotten, too.
你想让我...晚安
You want me to-- Have a good night.
都找到谁了
Who did we reach?
《先驱报》《时代周刊》《今日美国》
Herald, The Times, USA Today.
好的  还要电台和有线新闻
All right, I want affiliate stations and cable news.
让卫星直播车停在门口
I want satellite trucks out there.
我要电视直播
I want this on live TV.
好的  这就去办
Okay, I'm on it.
你们不能在这儿办
You can't do this here.
佐伊  今晚八点  科茨沃斯酒店
Zoe, 8 P.M. tonight, Hotel Cotesworth.
我妻子慈善机构的募捐晚宴
Benefit for my wife's charity.
不  脸洗干净  头发放下来
No, wash your face and let your hair down.
这既是工作也有乐子
This is work and play.
回见
See you.
我现在就跟你说  我要两打
I can tell you right now I'm going to need two dozen.
保罗  我明天就要  明白吗
Paul, I'm going to need those by tomorrow, okay?
你的客人是你的问题  与我无关  朱利安
Your guests are your problem, not mine, Julian.
我要关大门
I'll close the gate.
防火规章我不太懂
You know, I'm no expert in fire code,
不过我想把客人关在里面
but I would imagine that locking your guests in
比让他们随意走动更违规
is a bigger violation than having them walk around us.
这是非法侵入私人领地
This is trespassing on private property.
你这是违法
You're breaking the law.
好的  行
Right, okay.
我帮你接巴尼・豪尔
Let me get Barney Hull on the phone here for you.
给你
Here you go.
铃在响
It's ringing.
谁是巴尼・豪尔
Who's Barney Hull?
警察局长
The police commissioner.
不要吗  好
No? Okay.
你想当面和他谈也行
You'd rather talk to him in person, that's great.
他会来派对
He's coming to the party.
我一定向他介绍你
I'll be sure to introduce him to you.
谢谢你的款待
Thanks for your hospitality.
吧台移到这边
Bar comes over here.
酒都放那里去
Put all that booze that way.
你要我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
我不能锁门  他们有警察撑腰
I can't lock the gates, and they've got the police on their side.
难以置信  稍等
Unbelievable. Hold on.
卡珊德拉
Cassandra,
找两百名老师
I need 200 teachers
现在去科茨沃斯酒店
at the Cotesworth Hotel right now.
我要进行大规模示威
I need a full picket.
两百  我不确定能不能
200? I don't know if we can get that--
我不想听  搞定就是了
I don't want to hear it. Just get it done.
坦白说  我根本不在乎他们是不是老师
I don't give a fuck if they're teachers or not, frankly.
给我找两百个活人
Just get me 200 bodies.
打给卡车司机工会  也许他们会帮忙
You know, call the teamsters. Maybe they'll help us.
大不了给他们副眼镜
We'll give them glasses if we have to.
让他们打扮精神点
Tell the guys to look smart.
查理  电话挂了
Charlie, get off the phone.
我这就需要标语牌  至少一百块
I need signs right now, at least a hundred.
你知道吗  让他们去吧
You know what? Let them set it up.
这样反而对我们有利
It's actually better for us that way.
他们没法躲开我们
This way they can't hide from us.
你让我很难做
You've put me in a terrible situation.
非常感谢你的帮助
Thank you very much for all your help.
感激不尽
Much appreciated.
这里  标语牌在这里
Here, we got the signs right here.
快发给大家
Let's hand them out fast.
沿着这条街  一列横队
Everybody single file right down the street.
从这儿到那儿  懂吗
This way, that way. Okay?
去死安德伍德
好吧  至少他拼对了
Well, at least he spelled it right.
一群教师突然聚集在
Teachers protesting the education reform
教师工会抗议  净水计划庆典照常进行
华盛顿科茨沃斯酒店外
and achievement act have descended upon
抗议《教育改革和成就法案》
the Hotel Cotesworth in Washington, D.C.
工会说客马蒂・斯比奈拉组织了示威
Union lobbyist Martin Spinella organized the demonstration.
教师应受尊重
Teachers deserve respect!
我就知道你会来
Now, I knew you'd show up.
你带漂亮太太来了吗  你好
You bring that beautiful wife of yours? Hello...
很荣幸  谢谢你们来
Pleasure. Thank you for coming.
进去吧  饮料免费
Come on in. The drinks are on the house.
费莉希蒂
Felicity.
斯比奈拉让工会把我们拒之门外
Spinella got us shut out by the union,
所以我们就在酒店台阶上开派对
so we had to have the party out here on the steps.
我这就带你去吧台
I'll take you up to a bar right now.
谢谢你们赏光
Thank you for coming.
谢谢  欢迎
Thank you. Welcome.
教师万岁  工会万岁
Teachers, yes! Unions, yes!
再次感谢你们能来
Thanks again so much for coming.
亚当来了
Adam's here.
你来了
You came.
看上去很棒
Looks wonderful.
你得靠边了
You're going to have to move over,
我要亲自招待这对了不起的夫妇
because I have to serve this wonderful couple myself.
简直太棒了
This is fabulous.
只有克莱尔想得到
Only Claire could've thought of this.
你那儿有纯麦芽酒吗
I don't suppose you have anything single-malt back there.
弗兰克  看你当酒保真是物有所值
Frank, it's worth every penny to see you on keg duty.
那你说这杯酒是不是还能升值啊
Well, then don't you think this is worth just a few extra pennies?
我们该拿支票簿了  查尔斯
Oh, let's break out the checkbook, Charles.
你回复了吗
Did you RSVP?
我想这不重要
I assumed it didn't matter.
说得对
It doesn't.
很高兴你来了
I'm glad you're here.
我听了你的留言
When I heard your message.
我不该说那些话的  亚当
You know, I shouldn't have left that, Adam.
为什么
Why not?
也许我们该找时间聊聊
Maybe we should talk at some point.
把支票开大点  好吧
Make that check with a lot of zeroes, won't you?
好了
There we are.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
干杯
Cheers.
既然你来了  我得求你件大事
I'm going to ask a huge favor of you since you're here.
你想让我去招待人
You want to put me to work.
对  拜托了
Yes, please.
-乐意效劳  -来吧
- My pleasure. - Come.
这些精彩的照片出自一位
So these are some wonderful photographs
-优秀摄影师之手  -吉莉安
- by an amazing photographer-- - Gillian.
亚当・嘉乐威  很高兴见到你
Adam Galloway, nice to meet you.
这位就是摄影师本人
And this is the photographer himself.
弗莱迪
Freddie.
我只想好好谢谢你
I just wanted to thank you so much.
做得太棒了
Such a success.
我很荣幸  很荣幸
My pleasure. My pleasure.
他是最好的
He's the best.
我看到亚当来了
I see Adam's here.
我也不知道他会来
I didn't know he was coming.
-猜猜我弄到了什么  -什么
- Well, guess what I got. - What?
霍博恩夫妇又开了一张6万元支票
Another check from the Holburns for $60,000.
快  好好夸夸我吧
Come on, praise me like you should.
如果弗兰克・安德伍德和美国国会...
If Frank Underwood and the United States Congress--
我叫佐伊・巴恩斯  是头条网的
Hi, my name is Zoe Barnes. I'm with Slugline.
践踏美国教师的权益
...dismantle the rights of the American teacher?
工会万岁  教师万岁
Unions, yes! Teachers, yes!
你们为什么在这里抗议
Hi. Why do you protest here?
国会要慎重对待这个问题
And Congress has to take this seriously.
我们为了教师而来
We're here for the teachers.
我们在这儿...
We're here--
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
我们的要求并不过分
We're not asking for the world,
国会得站出来  把事情解决
and Congress needs to step up and get this done.
失陪
Excuse me.
裙子看着很眼熟
That dress looks familiar.
去音乐会那天穿的那条
It's the one I wore to the symphony.
没错  我们彼此欣赏的那天
Oh, yes, mutual admiration society.
没错
That's right.
有什么消息给我吗
So what do you have for me?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你周围全是华盛顿名流
Well, you're surrounded by Washington's elite.
你没听到任何
Are you saying you've overheard nothing
会对你我有用的话吗
that could be useful to either of us?
我在报道抗议事件
I'm covering the protest.
全世界都在报道抗议事件
The rest of the world is covering the protest.
你也许没注意到
You may not have noticed,
但你是唯一参加派对的记者
but you're the only journalist inside the party.
我给你的东西很多了
I've been feeding you plenty.
消息该是互通的  巴恩斯小姐
Information is a two-way street, Miss Barnes.
-你好  -克莱尔  这是佐伊・巴恩斯
- Hello. - Claire, this is Zoe Barnes.
那晚你们在家见过
You met her one night at the house.
我记得
Yes, I remember.
你在《先驱报》工作  对吗
You work for the Herald, right?
已经不在了
Not anymore.
我现在在头条网工作
I actually work at Slugline now.
我听说过那里
I've heard of it.
你读他们的报道  对吗  弗朗西斯
You read it, don't you, Francis?
忠实读者
Religiously.
你看来是位很有进取心的女孩
Well, you seem like a very ambitious young woman.
我很喜欢
I like that.
我在努力
Doing my best.
很高兴再次见到你
It's good to see you again.
玩得开心点
Please enjoy yourself.
会的  谢谢
I will. Thank you.
保重  巴恩斯小姐
Take care, Miss Barnes.
我什么都没有了  你害得我和孩子流落街头  你这个叛徒
你这么欺骗我  是为了什么  我想知道
罗素  吃屎去吧
真为你感到丢脸
你是好人  还是我想错了  你能帮我吗  苏珊・乔治
亲爱的苏珊  我知道你现在一定很受伤
我知道你认为这是我的错
你不是唯一这么想的
你没错  我是好人
至少我想做个好人
造船厂必须关闭的原因是....
我这次无法力争的原因是...
站在台阶上
...on the steps,
非常漂亮
and she looks gorgeous,
但其实她在想
but what really she's thinking,
我什么时候才能回家
when can I go the fuck home?
-我要走了  -这么早就走
- I'm off. - Already?
我想我的任务已经完成了
I've done my duty, I believe.
你了解我的
Oh, you know me.
总是第一个离开派对的人
Always have to be the first to leave a party.
已经筹集多少了
How much did you raise?
七十五万
$750,000.
其中八万来自你的照片
80 of that was your photographs.
太棒了
Fantastic.
再写张二十五万的支票  我们就有一百万了
Write a check for 250, we'll break a million.
想得美
Nice try.
感谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
以及你所做的一切
And everything that you did.
有空给我电话
Call me sometime.
我会的
I will.
净水慈善庆典
So what does a Clean Water gala
和教师工会有什么关系呢
have to do with teachers' unions?
超过50位国会议员就聚集在那里
Well, we have over 50 members of Congress gathered in one place.
但他们却都倡议
But the fact that these members of Congress are promoting
将钱投往国外
pouring money out of the country
而忽视本国的教师
while neglecting their teachers at home
这就是个问题
is precisely the problem.
但这是私人款项  不是公共税收  那么...
But this is private money, not public tax dollars, so...
我们不是在抗议活动本身
But we're not protesting the cause.
而是在抗议这些国会议员
We're protesting the Congressmen and women themselves.
这些抗议者都是教师吗
Are these even teachers picketing?
当然  一部分是
Well, sure, some of them.
还有一部分人是...
And some of them are people in--
不好意思
Excuse me.
弗兰克  你在
Frank. What are you--?
别拿食物  我们回头发食物
Don't take the food. We'll feed you later.
马蒂  你知道那句老话吧
Marty, you know that old saying.
世上最危险的事
The most dangerous spot in the world
就是不让卡车司机吃东西
is to come between a teamster and free food.
别拿食物  我们回头发食物
Don't take the food. We're feeding you later.
-我要拿  -她要拿
- I'll take it. - She'll take it.
还有谁饿了吗
Who else is hungry?
-给你  -传到后面去
- There you go. - Pass it back.
还有很多呢  各位
Plenty more coming, guys.
我知道你们在这儿待了几小时了
I know you've all been out here for hours.
谢谢  弗莱迪
Thank you, Freddy.
特区最好的肋排
The best ribs in D.C.
马蒂  来吧
Marty, come on.
你已经阐明观点  也上了新闻
You said your piece. You got on the news.
过来放松一下吧
Come and enjoy yourself.
我尊重你  克莱尔
I respect you, Claire.
但你知道我不能那样做
You know I can't do that.
不论你站在哪一边
Doesn't matter what side you're on.
大家都得吃东西
Everybody's got to eat.
来一盘肋排吧
You can have a plate of ribs.
没关系的  来吧
Yes, you can. Come on.
-不行  -可以的
- I can't. - Yes, you can.
谢谢  克莱尔  但真的不行
Thank you, Claire, but I cannot.
-可以的  来吧  -谢谢
- You can do it. Come on, - Thank you,
-马蒂  拜托  -真不行  谢谢  谢谢
- Marty. Come on. -I can't. Thank you. Thank you.
弗莱迪餐馆   去弗莱迪烧烤餐馆吃饭吧
Freddy's. You should go to Freddy's.
教师抗议净水计划庆典  抗议者为肋排不顾劝说
几十名工会支持者
Several dozen union sympathizers
在工会说客马蒂・斯比奈拉的带领下
led by labor lobbyist Martin Spinella
试图破坏慈善庆典
attempted to disrupt the gala.
他们得行动起来
They need to step up to the plate
关心我们的教师和孩子
and take care of our teachers and our children.
随着参加捐款的人向示威人群分发食物
The protest dissipated when fundraiser attendees
抗议也不了了之
offer food and drink to picketers.
不论你站在哪一边
Doesn't matter what side you're on.
大家都得吃东西
Everybody's gotta eat.
关掉
Turn it off.
抗议是否会继续尚不清楚
It is unclear whether the protest will continue.
现在该怎么办
What now?
给工会首脑和各分会主席打电话
Call the union leadership and the chapter presidents.
看他们准备好了没
See if they're ready to pull the trigger.
如果准备好了
If they are,
我们明天午夜开始罢工
we strike at midnight tomorrow.
你太棒了
You were extraordinary.
明天  没到场的人
Tomorrow, people who weren't there
也会撒谎说他们去了
are gonna lie and say they were.
你在看什么
What are you reading?
净水冲走工会
她挺能写的
She can write.
是啊
She can.
而你挺能筹钱的
And you can raise money.
只为正当理由
Always for a good cause.
谢谢你
Thank you.
请待在车里
Wait in the car, please.
等等  我认识他
Hold on. I know who that is.
你好  彼得
Hello, Peter.
我快饿死了  忘记吃东西了
I am starving. I forgot to eat.
要吃点什么吗  彼得
Would you like something, Peter?
不用了  谢谢
No. Thanks.
吃点吧
You should eat.
别争了  争不过她的
Don't fight. She'll win.
是啊
I will.
那好吧
Okay. Yes.
要来点咖啡吗
You want some coffee?
好的  谢谢
Yes. Thanks.
你有孩子吗
Do you have any children?
两个  一儿一女
Two. A son and a daughter.
结婚了
Married?
离婚了
Divorced.
你的小孩叫什么
What are their names, your kids?
女儿萨拉  11岁
Um, Sarah, she's 11,
儿子凯文  八岁
and Kevin is eight.
有照片吗
Do you have any pictures?
靠  手机丢了
Fuck! I lost my phone.
抱歉  我得走了
I..sorry. I should...uh, I gotta go.
彼得  坐下
Peter, sit down.
你要好好享用三明治
You're gonna enjoy your sandwich,
喝点咖啡  在这儿过夜
have some coffee, and stay the night.
加牛奶和糖吗
Milk and sugar?
都不加
Black.
这里有新毛巾
Some fresh towels.
浴室里肥皂和牙膏
There should be soap and toothpaste,
什么都有
everything you need in the bathroom.
真是太感谢了
Thank you so much for doing this.
没事  好梦
Oh, it's nothing. Sleep well.
怎么回事  彼得
What's going on, Peter?
和我说说
Talk to me.
你觉得给我新毛巾就完事了吗
You think fresh towels changes anything?
什么事
Changes what?
造船厂
The shipyard.
如果是在我家乡  你给我来那套
If I was home and you pulled that shit,
我一定打死你
I'd beat the fuck out of you.
我会在人行道上敲碎你的脑袋
I would crack your skull on the pavement.
我今天就是为这个而来
That's why I came over here today,
为你逼我做的事好好教训你
to fuck you up for what you made me do.
我不管你对我多好
I don't care how nice you're being to me.
我才不管
I don't give a shit.
明早起来
I'm gonna wake up tomorrow...
这些人
and all these people...
我的朋友
all my friends...
还是一团糟
are still fucked.
我也还是一团糟
And I'm still fucked.
都是你害的
You fucked all of us.
背黑锅的却是我
But I'm gonna get blamed for it.
于是我得承担这份重担
So now I have to carry that weight on my shoulders.
你害了我  弗兰克
You fucked me, Frank.
我不该让你那么做  可我没反抗
I shouldn't have let you do it, but I did.
你抱怨完了吗
Are you done now?
起来
Get up.
-不要  -给我站起来
- No. - I said get up.
跟我来  马上
And follow me. Now.
进来
Get in.
把衣服脱了  坐进去
Take off your clothes and get in.
现在就做
Do it. Now.
这周早些时候有场民主党全国委员会会议
There was a D.N.C. meeting earlier this week.
关于州长竞选
About the governor's race.
你作为人选之一被提及了
Your name came up as someone we might want to run.
阿司匹林  吃吧
Aspirin. Go ahead.
其他人都说你不值得考虑
Everyone in that room wanted to cross you off the list.
我反对  我替你说话了
I said no. I stuck up for you.
我说"彼得・罗素这人有潜力"
I said, "Peter Russo, he's got potential."
"他年轻  有能力  必有发展"
"He's young. He's capable. He's going places."
我让他们继续考虑你
I made them keep you in contention.
你还在那名单上
You're still on that list.
你半夜出现在我家
You show up at my house in the middle of the night,
醉醺醺  撒怨气
drunk, to whine,
还想反过来怪我
to try to shift the blame on me
而不是为你自己和你的行为负责
instead of taking responsibility for yourself and your own actions.
或许会议上他们是对的
Maybe they were right in that meeting.
也许你就是没用
Maybe you are worthless.
我是唯一相信你的人  彼得
I'm the only person who believes in you, Peter,
但或许我也不该信你
but maybe that's one too many.
热水会舒张你的毛细管
The hot water will open up your capillaries.
你刚吃的阿司匹林会稀释你的血液
The aspirin you just took will make your blood thinner.
由你决定了  彼得
It's up to you, Peter.
如果你真决定以懦弱的方式解脱
Oh, and if you do decide to take the coward's way out,
沿血管割  不要横着割
cut along the tracks, not across them.
那是低级错误
That's a rookie mistake.
早
Morning.
要搭便车去国会吗
You need a lift to The Hill?
我得回家换衣服
I should go home and change my clothes.
没事  我们送你去
No, no, we'll drop you.
要咖啡吗
Want some coffee?
弗兰克
Frank...
给你一个月
One month.
一个月戒酒
One month sober.
我向你保证
I can give you that.
不是向我  是向你自己
Not for me. For you.
他真下决心了吗
Has the seed been planted?
只有彼得能回答这问题
Only Peter can answer that question.
选择在他
He has a choice.
萎靡不振还是重振旗鼓
Will he wither or will he thrive?
只有时间能证明
Only time will tell.
■
本集开篇佐伊在考虑接受哪份职位时提到了多家新闻机构
CBS著名的《60分钟》是公共台唯一收视率排前五的新闻节目
所以佐伊说CBS找她作记者说明她很受欢迎
MSNBC  FOX NEWS和CNN是三家有线新闻台  只播出新闻
CNN名气大  资格老  但目前收视率最低
FOX NEWS的收视率往往能高于另外两家之和
MSNBC是后起之秀  现已将CNN远远甩开
FOX NEWS倾向共和党  MSNBC倾向民主党
CNN相对中立  略偏向民主党
而政治新闻网原来是一家华盛顿小报  但目前主要业务是网站
报道美国时政  近几年影响力越来愈大  美国政府和国会内部人员会看
头条网则是虚构的
■
这一集还提到了大选中所谓的"摇摆州"
美国50个州  有40个的支持倾向明确  每次大选投票结果可以预测
最关键有10个州每次选举结果不确定  也是大选时候选人的主攻方向
还有一个概念叫选区重划
之前说过众议员选举根据各州人数决定
美国每10年进行一次人口普查
然后根据新的人口数据重新分配各州众议员名额
各州的议会再开会重新划选区  通过划选区
有时候可以决定在这个选区哪个党的选民多
从而为该党派多选出议员
■
会议一段还提到sex offender sting
是指美国执法机构进行钓鱼执法
在网上论坛冒充未成年人约变态到特定地点约会
然后将其逮捕  而这些人即使服刑出狱
也要记录在案  不能在学校附近居住
翻译  小蟹
翻译  u油
翻译  天意
翻译  痒痒和他的小跟班儿
翻译  音司忐忑
翻译  ~某人
翻译  小饭
翻译  泽川
翻译  噎死青春
翻译  某羽
时间轴  Poxle   吉吉
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第五集
人人影视倾情奉献